ILGWU Political Department Records 5780/103
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- "S" General, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Salt II, 1978-1981 (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Senate - General, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 7)
- Southeast Region, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 8)
- Staff Mailings, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 9)
- Sweatshops, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 10)
- Subscription List Distribution, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 11)
- "T" General, 1980-1981 (Box 30, Folder 12)
- Evelyn Dubrow Statement on S. 227 - Trade Adjustment Assistance Amendments, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  July 9
- Statements Before the Trade Policy Staff Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 30, Folder 14)
- U.S. Consumer Product Safety Commission, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 15)
- Hearings on Unemployment Compensation, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 16)
- Union Health Center, 1963 (Box 30, Folder 17)
- Upper South Region, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 18)
- "W" General, 1980-1981 (Box 30, Folder 19)
- Western States, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 20)
- "C" General, 1981-1982 (Box 30, Folder 21)
- Candidates' Addresses, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 22)
- Center for the Family, 1974-1975 (Box 30, Folder 23)
- Central States Region, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 24)
- Consumer Federation of America, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 25)
- Commission on Presidential Nomination and Party Structure, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 26)
- House of Representatives, 1981-1982 (Box 30, Folder 27)
- Congressional Hispanic Caucus, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 28)
- Consumer Affairs Lists (Box 30, Folder 29)
- Consumer Legislation, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 30)
- Cope Political Memos, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 31)
- Correspondence Committees, 1981-1982 (Box 30, Folder 32)
- Deficits, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 33)
- Democratic Party, 1981-1982 (Box 30, Folder 34)
- Democratic Study Group, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 35)
- Democratic National Committee, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 36)
- ERA, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 37)
- Eastern Pennsylvania Region, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 38)
- Evelyn Dubrow Expenses, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 39)
- Evelyn Dubrow Personal Expenses, 1975-1977 (Box 30, Folder 40)
- Evelyn Dubrow Income Taxes, 1967-1971 (Box 30, Folder 41)
- "F" General, 1978-1982 (Box 30, Folder 42)
- Federationist, 1981-1982 (Box 30, Folder 43)
- Pamela Freer Correspondence with Evelyn Dubrow, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 44)
- Frontlash, 1982 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- "G" General, 1982 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- Inter-Office, 1982 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- GEB Reports, 1981-1982 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Group Research (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Housing, 1981-1982 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- "How Our Laws Are Made", 1974-1978 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- "J" General, 1982 (Box 31, Folder 8)
- Jewish Labor Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 31, Folder 9)
- "K" General, 1982 (Box 31, Folder 10)
- "L" General, 1982 (Box 31, Folder 11)
- Labor - General, 1982 (Box 31, Folder 12)
- Legislative Alerts, 1981-1982 (Box 31, Folder 13)
- Lobby Reports, 1982 (Box 31, Folder 14)
- "M" General, 1981-1982 (Box 31, Folder 15)
- Midwest Region, 1982 (Box 31, Folder 16)
- "N" General, 1982 (Box 31, Folder 17)
- National Civic Review, 1982 (Box 31, Folder 18)
- New England Region, 1982 (Box 31, Folder 19)
- Newspaper Clippings, 1982 (Box 31, Folder 20)
- New Jersey Region, 1982 (Box 31, Folder 21)
- New York City Locals, 1982 (Box 31, Folder 22)
- New York State District, 1982 (Box 31, Folder 23)
- National Civic Review, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 24)
- Washington, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 25)
- "A" General, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 26)
- Cope - General, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 27)
- November, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- October, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 2)
- August, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- June, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- May, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 5)
- April, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 6)
- March, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 7)
- February, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 8)
- January, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 9)
- Southeast Region, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 10)
- Northeast Department, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 11)
- New York State, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 12)
- New Jersey Region, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 13)
- Central States, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 14)
- Eastern Pennsylvania, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 15)
- New England, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 16)
- Lobby Reports, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 17)
- New York City Locals, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 18)
- Form Letters, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 19)
- AFL-CIO Statements, 1982-1983 (Box 32, Folder 20)
- The Joyce Annual Foundation Report, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 21)
- The Federation, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 22)
- Harvard, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 23)
- NAACP, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 24)
- Civil Rights Update, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 25)
- Congress, 1981-1983 (Box 32, Folder 26)
- Names of Congressmen for Christmas Gifts, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 27)
- Congressional Budget, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 28)
- Coalition of Labor Union Women, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 29)
- Local News, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 30)
- AFL-CIO News, 1981 (Box 32, Folder 31)
- AFL-CIO News, 1981 (Box 32, Folder 32)
- Miscellaneous, 1980-1984 (Box 32, Folder 33)
- Garment Center Rally, 1983-1984 (Box 32, Folder 34)
- S. Res 122, H. Res 172, 1983-1984 (Box 32, Folder 35)
- Senate - General, 1983-1984 (Box 32, Folder 36)
- Seniority, 1983-1984 (Box 32, Folder 37)
- Staff Members, 1982-1983 (Box 32, Folder 38)
- Telecopies Transmission Notes, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 39)
- "W" General, 1982-1984 (Box 32, Folder 40)
- Order Forms, 1974-1975 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- New Hampshire Special Election (John Dunkin), 1975 (Box 33, Folder 2)
- New Jersey Region, 1974-1975 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- New Mexico, 1974-1975 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- New York, 1974-1975 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- North Carolina, 1974-1975 (Box 33, Folder 6)
- North Dakota, 1974-1975 (Box 33, Folder 7)
- Ohio, 1974-1975 (Box 33, Folder 8)
- Oklahoma, 1974-1975 (Box 33, Folder 9)
- Oregon, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 10)
- Pennsylvania, 1974-1975 (Box 33, Folder 11)
- Rhode Island, 1974-1975 (Box 33, Folder 12)
- South Carolina, 1974-1975 (Box 33, Folder 13)
- South Dakota, 1974-1975 (Box 33, Folder 14)
- Tennessee, 1974-1975 (Box 33, Folder 15)
- Texas, 1974-1975 (Box 33, Folder 16)
- Utah, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 17)
- Virginia, 1974-1975 (Box 33, Folder 18)
- Vermont, 1974-1975 (Box 33, Folder 19)
- Washington, 1974-1975 (Box 33, Folder 20)
- West Virginia, 1974-1975 (Box 33, Folder 21)
- Wisconsin, 1974-1975 (Box 33, Folder 22)
- Wyoming, 1974-1975 (Box 33, Folder 23)
- Form Letters, 1972 (Box 33, Folder 24)
- Orders for Campaign Material, 1974-1975 (Box 33, Folder 25)
- Bills, 1972-1975 (Box 33, Folder 26)
- Campaign Coordinators, 1974-1975 (Box 33, Folder 27)
- Congressional Black Caucus Dinner, 1974-1975 (Box 33, Folder 28)
- Campaign Set-up, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 29)
- Inter-Office, 1974-1975 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Campaign Committee Contributions, 1968-1975 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Congratulatory Letters, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Campaign Report Laws, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Campaign Practices Reports (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 6)
- National Democratic Committee, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 7)
- Special Receipt Books, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 8)
- Small Receipt Books, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 9)
- Large Receipt Books, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 10)
- Subscription Lists, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 11)
- Orders for Campaign Leaflets and Posters, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 12)
- AFL-CIO Cope, 1974-1975 (Box 34, Folder 13)
- Democratic Congressional Dinner Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 34, Folder 14)
- Coalition for a Democratic Majority, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 15)
- Democratic - General, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 16)
- Individual Contributions, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 17)
- Central States Region, 1974-1975 (Box 34, Folder 18)
- Cloak Out-of-Town Department, 1974-1975 (Box 34, Folder 19)
- Eastern Region, 1974-1975 (Box 34, Folder 20)
- Midwest Region, 1974-1975 (Box 34, Folder 21)
- New York City Locals, 1974-1975 (Box 34, Folder 22)
- Northeast Department, 1974-1975 (Box 34, Folder 23)
- Ohio-Kentucky Region, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 24)
- Southeast Region, 1974-1975 (Box 34, Folder 25)
- South Jersey-Philadelphia Region, 1974-1975 (Box 34, Folder 26)
- Upper South Department, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 27)
- Western States, 1974-1975 (Box 34, Folder 28)
- Requests for Contributors, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 29)
- Alaska, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 30)
- Alabama, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 31)
- Arkansas, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 32)
- Arizona, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 33)
- California, 1974-1975 (Box 34, Folder 34)
- Colorado, 1974-1975 (Box 34, Folder 35)
- Delaware, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 36)
- Connecticut, 1974-1975 (Box 34, Folder 37)
- Florida, 1974-1975 (Box 34, Folder 38)
- Georgia, 1974-1975 (Box 34, Folder 39)
- Idaho, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 40)
- Illinois, 1974-1975 (Box 34, Folder 41)
- Indiana, 1974-1975 (Box 34, Folder 42)
- Iowa, 1974-1975 (Box 34, Folder 43)
- Kansas, 1974-1975 (Box 34, Folder 44)
- Kentucky, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 45)
- Louisiana, 1974-1975 (Box 34, Folder 46)
- Maine, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 47)
- Maryland, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 48)
- Massachusetts, 1974-1975 (Box 34, Folder 49)
- Michigan, 1974-1975 (Box 34, Folder 50)
- Minnesota, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 51)
- Mississippi, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 52)
- Missouri, 1974-1975 (Box 34, Folder 53)
- Montana, 1974-1975 (Box 34, Folder 54)
- Nebraska, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 55)
- Nebraska, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 56)
- New Hampshire, 1974-1975 (Box 34, Folder 57)
- AFL-CIO News, 1982-1983 (Box 35, Folder 1)
- AFL-CIO Bulletins, 1982-1983 (Box 35, Folder 2)
- Cope Operating Committee, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- Cope Financial Reports, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 4)
- American Textile Manufacturers Institute, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 5)
- "C" General, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 6)
- Coalition of Labor Union Women, 1982-1983 (Box 35, Folder 7)
- Commentary, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 8)
- "D" General, 1982 (Box 35, Folder 9)
- Democratic National Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 35, Folder 10)
- Committees of Correspondence, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 11)
- Consumer Federation of America, 1981-1983 (Box 35, Folder 12)
- Congressional Hispanic Caucus, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 13)
- Evelyn Dubrow Personal, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 14)
- Evelyn Dubrow Expenses, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 15)
- Iris Sunshine Expenses, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 16)
- "G" General, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 17)
- GEB Report, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 18)
- "H" General, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 19)
- Inter-Office, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 20)
- Invoices, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 21)
- Justice, 1981-1983 (Box 35, Folder 22)
- "L" General, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 23)
- Correspondence with Washington, DC, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 24)
- "M" General, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 25)
- "N" General, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 26)
- ILGWU Campaign Committee, 1982 (Box 35, Folder 27)
- Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Orders for Leaflets, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 2)
- Form Letters, 1976-1977 (Box 36, Folder 3)
- Congressional Black Caucus Dinner, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 4)
- Committee for a Democratic Majority, 1975-1976 (Box 36, Folder 5)
- Class of 74, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 6)
- Democratic Congressional Dinner Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 36, Folder 7)
- Democratic National Committee, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 8)
- Democratic Study Groups, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 9)
- Machinists Non-Partisan Political League, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 10)
- Contributions - New Jersey State Committee, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 11)
- English Leaflets, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 12)
- Spanish and English Leaflets, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 13)
- Spanish Posters, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 14)
- English Posters, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 15)
- Miscellaneous Contributions, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 16)
- Alaska, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 17)
- California, 1976-1977 (Box 36, Folder 18)
- Arizona, 1976-1977 (Box 36, Folder 19)
- Arkansas, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 20)
- Colorado, 1976-1977 (Box 36, Folder 21)
- Connecticut, 1976-1977 (Box 36, Folder 22)
- Delaware, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 23)
- Florida, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 24)
- Georgia, 1976-1977 (Box 36, Folder 25)
- Hawaii, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 26)
- Idaho, 1976-1977 (Box 36, Folder 27)
- Illinois, 1976-1977 (Box 36, Folder 28)
- Indiana, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 29)
- Iowa, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 30)
- Kansas, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 31)
- Kentucky, 1976-1977 (Box 36, Folder 32)
- Louisiana, 1976-1977 (Box 36, Folder 33)
- Maine, 1976-1977 (Box 36, Folder 34)
- Maryland, 1976-1977 (Box 36, Folder 35)
- Massachusetts, 1976-1977 (Box 36, Folder 36)
- Michigan, 1976-1977 (Box 36, Folder 37)
- Minnesota, 1976-1977 (Box 36, Folder 38)
- Mississippi, 1976-1977 (Box 36, Folder 39)
- Missouri, 1976-1977 (Box 36, Folder 40)
- Montana, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 41)
- Nebraska, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 42)
- Nevada, 1976-1977 (Box 36, Folder 43)
- Nebraska, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 44)
- New Hampshire, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 45)
- New Jersey, 1976-1977 (Box 36, Folder 46)
- New Mexico, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 47)
- New York, 1976-1977 (Box 36, Folder 48)
- New York, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 49)
- Ohio, 1976-1977 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- North Carolina, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- North Dakota, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 3)
- Oklahoma, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 4)
- Oregon, 1976-1977 (Box 37, Folder 5)
- Pennsylvania, 1976-1978 (Box 37, Folder 6)
- Puerto Rico, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Rhode Island, 1976-1977 (Box 37, Folder 8)
- South Carolina, 1976-1977 (Box 37, Folder 9)
- South Dakota, 1976-1977 (Box 37, Folder 10)
- Tennessee, 1976-1977 (Box 37, Folder 11)
- Texas, 1976-1978 (Box 37, Folder 12)
- Utah, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 13)
- Vermont, 1976-1977 (Box 37, Folder 14)
- Virginia, 1976-1977 (Box 37, Folder 15)
- Virgin Islands, 1977 (Box 37, Folder 16)
- Washington, 1976-1977 (Box 37, Folder 17)
- West Virginia, 1976-1977 (Box 37, Folder 18)
- Wisconsin, 1976-1977 (Box 37, Folder 19)
- Wyoming, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 20)
- Central States, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 21)
- Eastern Region, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 22)
- Midwest, 1976-1977 (Box 37, Folder 23)
- New England, 1976-1977 (Box 37, Folder 24)
- New York Locals, 1976-1977 (Box 37, Folder 25)
- Northeast Department, 1976-1977 (Box 37, Folder 26)
- Ohio-Kentucky Region, 1976-1977 (Box 37, Folder 27)
- South Jersey-Philadelphia Region, 1976-1977 (Box 37, Folder 28)
- Southeast, 1976-1977 (Box 37, Folder 29)
- Upper South, 1976-1977 (Box 37, Folder 30)
- Western States, 1976-1977 (Box 37, Folder 31)
- Letters of Congratulations and Replies, 1976-1977 (Box 37, Folder 32)
- Posters in English and Spanish (Box 37, Folder 33)
- Flyers (Box 37, Folder 34)
- Contributions - Oklahoma, 1978-1979 (Box 37, Folder 35)
- Contributions - Alaska, 1978-1979 (Box 37, Folder 36)
- Arizona, 1978-1979 (Box 37, Folder 37)
- Arkansas, 1978-1979 (Box 37, Folder 38)
- Colorado, 1978-1979 (Box 37, Folder 39)
- California, 1978-1979 (Box 37, Folder 40)
- Colorado, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 1)
- Connecticut, 1978-1979 (Box 38, Folder 2)
- Delaware, 1978-1979 (Box 38, Folder 3)
- Florida, 1978-1979 (Box 38, Folder 4)
- Georgia, 1978-1979 (Box 38, Folder 5)
- Hawaii, 1978-1979 (Box 38, Folder 6)
- Idaho, 1978-1979 (Box 38, Folder 7)
- Illinois, 1978-1980 (Box 38, Folder 8)
- Indiana, 1978-1979 (Box 38, Folder 9)
- Iowa, 1978-1979 (Box 38, Folder 10)
- Kansas, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 11)
- Kentucky, 1978-1979 (Box 38, Folder 12)
- Louisiana, 1978-1979 (Box 38, Folder 13)
- Maine, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 14)
- Maryland, 1978-1979 (Box 38, Folder 15)
- Massachusetts, 1978-1979 (Box 38, Folder 16)
- Michigan, 1978-1979 (Box 38, Folder 17)
- Minnesota, 1978-1979 (Box 38, Folder 18)
- Mississippi, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 19)
- Missouri, 1978-1979 (Box 38, Folder 20)
- Montana, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 21)
- Nebraska, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 22)
- Nevada, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 23)
- New Hampshire, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 24)
- New Jersey, 1978-1979 (Box 38, Folder 25)
- New Mexico, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 26)
- New York, 1978-1980 (Box 38, Folder 27)
- North Carolina, 1978-1979 (Box 38, Folder 28)
- North Dakota, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 29)
- Ohio, 1978-1979 (Box 38, Folder 30)
- Oklahoma, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 31)
- Oregon, 1978-1979 (Box 38, Folder 32)
- Pennsylvania, 1978-1979 (Box 39, Folder 1)
- Rhode Island, 1978-1979 (Box 39, Folder 2)
- South Carolina, 1978-1979 (Box 39, Folder 3)
- South Dakota, 1978-1979 (Box 39, Folder 4)
- Tennessee, 1978-1979 (Box 39, Folder 5)
- Texas, 1978-1979 (Box 39, Folder 6)
- Utah, 1978-1979 (Box 39, Folder 7)
- Vermont, 1978-1979 (Box 39, Folder 8)
- Virginia, 1978 (Box 39, Folder 9)
- Virgin Islands, 1978 (Box 39, Folder 10)
- Washington, 1978-1979 (Box 39, Folder 11)
- West Virginia, 1978-1979 (Box 39, Folder 12)
- Wisconsin, 1978-1979 (Box 39, Folder 13)
- Wyoming, 1978 (Box 39, Folder 14)
- Central States Region, 1978-1979 (Box 39, Folder 15)
- Eastern Region, 1978-1979 (Box 39, Folder 16)
- Eastern Pennsylvania Region, 1978-1979 (Box 39, Folder 17)
- Midwest Region, 1978-1979 (Box 39, Folder 18)
- New England Region, 1978-1979 (Box 39, Folder 19)
- New York City Locals, 1978-1979 (Box 39, Folder 20)
- New York State District, 1978-1979 (Box 39, Folder 21)
- Ohio-Kentucky Region, 1978 (Box 39, Folder 22)
- Northeast Department, 1978-1979 (Box 39, Folder 23)
- Southeast Department, 1978-1979 (Box 39, Folder 24)
- Upper South Department, 1978-1979 (Box 39, Folder 25)
- Western States Region, 1978-1979 (Box 39, Folder 26)
- Individual Contributions, 1978-1979 (Box 39, Folder 27)
- Contributions by Staff Members to ILGWU Campaign Fund, 1978-1979 (Box 39, Folder 28)
- Inter-Office, 1978-1979 (Box 39, Folder 29)
- Leaflets (Box 39, Folder 30)
- AFL-CIO Cope, 1978-1979 (Box 39, Folder 31)
- National Democratic Committee, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 32)
- Democratic Congressional Campaign Committee, 1978 (Box 39, Folder 33)
- New Jersey Democratic State Committee, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 34)
- New York State Democratic Committee, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 35)
- Miscellaneous Contributions, 1978 (Box 39, Folder 36)
- Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 39, Folder 37)
- Democratic Congressional Dinner Committee, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 38)
- Democratic Senatorial Campaign Committee, 1978 (Box 39, Folder 39)
- Annual Black Caucus Dinner, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 40)
- Bills, 1978-1979 (Box 39, Folder 41)
- Campaign Committee Orders (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Form Letters, 1978-1979 (Box 40, Folder 2)
- Contributions to Candidates, 1978 (Box 40, Folder 3)
- Lists of Contributions, 1978 (Box 40, Folder 4)
- Contributions, 1978 (Box 40, Folder 5)
- Campaign Payroll and Expenses, 1978 (Box 40, Folder 6)
- Campaign Flyers (Box 40, Folder 7)
  In Spanish
- Advertising other than Leeds, 1960-1961 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  In English and Yiddish
- Rally Expenses, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 9)
- Clippings, 1960-1961 (Box 40, Folder 10)
- Bills - Paid, 1960-1961 (Box 40, Folder 11)
- Radio and Recording Tapes, 1960-1961 (Box 40, Folder 12)
- Radio Station KMAC, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 13)
- Receipts - Button Payments and Report, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 14)
- Disbursements, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 15)
- Bills - Rally, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  in English and Italian
- Printing, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 17)
- Miscellaneous, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 18)
- Photography, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 19)
- Miscellaneous Invoices and Bills, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 20)
- Radio, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 21)
- Final Political Reports, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 22)
- Memos from M. Bialis - Midwest, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 23)
- Finances, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 24)
- Philadelphia Expenses - Final Report, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 25)
- Boston Expenses, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 26)
- Cloak Out-of-Town Department, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 27)
- South Jersey-Philadelphia Expenses, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 28)
- COT Expenses, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 29)
- Final Reports, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 30)
- Final Reports - No CC, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 31)
- Ohio-Kentucky Final Report, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 32)
- MW - No Campaign Committee, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 33)
- Central - No Campaign Committee, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 34)
- Dress Joint Board - No Expenses, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 35)
- Joint Board of Cloakmakers - No Expenses, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 36)
- Cloak Out-of-Town - No Expenses, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 37)
- New York City Miscellaneous, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 38)
- MW Expenses, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 39)
- Money to Midwest Department - No Expenses, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 40)
- Central - No Expenses, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 41)
- Upper South, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 42)
- Northeast Department, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 43)
- ILGWU Fund Committee, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 44)
- Pacific Coast Expenses, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 45)
- Ohio-Kentucky Expenses, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 46)
- Northeast Department Expenses, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 47)
- Southeast Department Expenses, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 48)
- Eastern Region, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 49)
- Northeast Department - No Expenses, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 50)
- New York City Miscellaneous Expenses, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 51)
- Miscellaneous Expenses (Box 40, Folder 52)
- October, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- November, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 2)
- Cloak Joint Board, Cloak Out-of-Town, and Dress Joint Board, 1972-1983 (Box 41, Folder 3)
- Local 10, 1972-1979 (Box 41, Folder 4)
- Local 20, 1972-1976 (Box 41, Folder 5)
- Local 23-25, 1974-1983 (Box 41, Folder 6)
- Local 38, 1972-1974 (Box 41, Folder 7)
- Local 40, 1972-1979 (Box 41, Folder 8)
- Local 62, 1972-1978 (Box 41, Folder 9)
- Local 66, 1972-1980 (Box 41, Folder 10)
- Local 91, 1978-1982 (Box 41, Folder 11)
- Local 98, 1972-1978 (Box 41, Folder 12)
- Local 99, 1972-1976 (Box 41, Folder 13)
- Local 105, 1972-1979 (Box 41, Folder 14)
- Local 132, 1972-1979 (Box 41, Folder 15)
- Local 155, 1972-1980 (Box 41, Folder 16)
- New York State District, 1978-1982 (Box 41, Folder 17)
- Northeast Department, 1975-1978 (Box 41, Folder 18)
- Local 93, 1972-1978 (Box 41, Folder 19)
- Local 111, 1972-1982 (Box 41, Folder 20)
- Local 118, 1972-1974 (Box 41, Folder 21)
- Local 185-306, 1973-1976 (Box 41, Folder 22)
- Local 226, 1973-1980 (Box 41, Folder 23)
- Local 295, 1972-1977 (Box 41, Folder 24)
- Northeast Department, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 25)
- Local 351, 1972-1983 (Box 41, Folder 26)
- Local 361, 1975-1978 (Box 41, Folder 27)
- New Jersey Region, 1972-1980 (Box 41, Folder 28)
- Boston Joint Board, 1972-1982 (Box 41, Folder 29)
- Central Pennsylvania District Council, 1973-1981 (Box 41, Folder 30)
- Easton District, 1976-1981 (Box 41, Folder 31)
- Eastern Pennsylvania Region, 1981 (Box 41, Folder 32)
- Hazleton District Council, 1973-1983 (Box 41, Folder 33)
- North New England District Council, 1972-1983 (Box 41, Folder 34)
- New York Coat, Suit, Dress, Rainwear, and Allied Workers Union, 1981 (Box 41, Folder 35)
- Ohio Region, 1974-1980 (Box 41, Folder 36)
- Scranton District Council, 1972-1981 (Box 41, Folder 37)
- Shamokin-Sunbury District Council, 1975-1982 (Box 41, Folder 38)
- Trenton-Wilmington District Council, 1972-1978 (Box 41, Folder 39)
- Upstate New York and Vermont, 1973-1974 (Box 41, Folder 40)
- Western Pennsylvania District Council, 1972-1982 (Box 41, Folder 41)
- Wyoming Valley District Council, 1978-1980 (Box 41, Folder 42)
- New England Region, 1977-1981 (Box 41, Folder 43)
- North New England Region, 1977-1979 (Box 41, Folder 44)
- Connecticut District Council, 1977-1978 (Box 41, Folder 45)
- South New England District Council, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 46)
- Western Massachusetts District Council, 1974-1978 (Box 41, Folder 47)
- Local 190, 1972-1975 (Box 41, Folder 48)
- Philadelphia Dress Joint Board, 1972-1976 (Box 41, Folder 49)
- South Jersey-Philadelphia Joint Board, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 50)
- Midwest Region, 1972-1978 (Box 41, Folder 51)
- Missouri-Mississippi River Valley District Council, 1981-1982 (Box 41, Folder 52)
- Eastern Missouri District Council, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 53)
- Kansas City Joint Board, 1973-1979 (Box 41, Folder 54)
- Missouri-Kansas-Nebraska, 1972-1974 (Box 41, Folder 55)
- St. Louis Joint Board, 1972-1977 (Box 41, Folder 56)
- Southern Illinois District Court, 1972-1978 (Box 41, Folder 57)
- Southern Missouri-Arkansas District Court, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 58)
- Texas-Oklahoma District Council, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 59)
- Southeast Region, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 60)
- Upper South Department, 1975-1980 (Box 41, Folder 61)
- New York State District, 1978-1980 (Box 41, Folder 62)
- San Francisco Joint Board, 1972-1977 (Box 41, Folder 63)